Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series X. Public Relations, 1975-1991; 153602; 22 Linear Feet in 47 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box.; 33 videocassettes (vhs)
  - Correspondence and Press Release on Commencement, 1990; 153838 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Memos and Related Material on Public Occasions, 1990; 153837 (Box 152, Folder 2-6)
  - Commencement, 1989; 153836 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Marymount College Tarrytown Commencement Program, 1991; 153835 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - "P.L. 94-142: Ten Years Later" Conference, 1985; 153834 (Box 153, Folder 2-3)
  - Letter to Craig Morgan, 1989; 153833 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - C. Walter Nichols Award, Kean College Convocation, 1991; 153832 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Giulio Andreotti, Carlos Salinas Visits, 1990; 153831 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Patriarch Demetrios I Visit, 1989; 153830 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation, 1991; 153829 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Invitations to Colin Powell and Elie Wiesel, 1989; 153828 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Declined Invitations, 1990; 153827 (Box 153, Folder 10-14)
  - Neighborhood Organizations, 1991; 153826 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Letter from Joe Dunbar, 1991; 153825 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square Park Involvement, 1990; 153824 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Organizations and Local Residents, 1989; 153823 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - "Spruce Up 90" Event, 1990; 153822 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Park Complaint, 1989; 153821 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - NYU Community Fund Remarks, The Caring Community, 1991; 153820 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - The Caring Community, Complaint, 1989; 153819 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990; 153818 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Local Residents, Traffic Issue, 1989; 153817 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Amnesty International, Campus Security, 1991; 153816 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Local Resident Concerns, 1989; 153815 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Memo to Lynne Brown, 1989; 153814 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Commencement, 1991; 153813 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Reports, Memos, Clippings, 1984; 153812 (Box 154, Folder 15-17)
  - Notre Dame Journal of Law, Ethics, and Public Policy, 1985; 153811 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Universities, Information Technologies, and Academic Libraries, 1981; 153810 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Third World Radical Regimes, 1985; 153809 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Arms Control Today, 1985; 153808 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Views in New York, 1980; 153807 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Humanities, 1985-1985; 153806 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - The New Deal: Fifty Years After, 1984; 153805 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Providing for the Needs of Black Students in the University, 1985; 153804 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Memo, 1984; 153803 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Publications, Press Releases, Memos, 1985; 153802 (Box 155, Folder 9-11, Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Speech Transcripts, 1984-1985; 153801 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Governors Conference, 1984-1985; 153800 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Other University Commencements, 1984-1985; 153799 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1985; 153798 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Dental, 1984-1985; 153797 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1984-1985; 153796 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Memos and Invitations to Public Occasions, 1984-1985; 153795 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Complaints and Responses RESTRICTED, 1984-1985; 153794 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Community Boards, The Public Agenda Foundation, 1984-1985; 153793 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park Cleanup, 1984-1985; 153792 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - PA Consulting, 1984; 153791 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - NYU Magazine Planning, 1985; 153790 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1985; 153789 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, 1984-1985; 153788 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Report, 1983-1985; 153787 (Box 158, Folder 1-3)
  - University Public Issues Committee, 1984; 153786 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1984-1985; 153785 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Convocations, 1984-1985 (Box 158, Folder 6-8)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1985; 153784 (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
  - Graduate Education, 1983-1984; 153783 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Condolences, 1984-1985; 153782 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Memos, Correspondence, Notes, 1983-1985; 153781 (Box 159, Folder 5-6)
  - Press Releases, Press Office Packets, Clippings, 1982-1985; 153780 (Box 160, Folder 1-4)
  - Press Releases, Memos, 1983-1985; 153779 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Fundraising Request, 1983-1985 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Duke of Alba, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Kriser Professorship in Anthropology, 1985 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Iakovos, 1984; 153778 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Press Clippings, 1984; 153777 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, Correspondence, 1985; 153776 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1984-1985; 153775 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, Newsletters, Lectures, 1984; 153774 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Letter from Police Assistant Chief, 1987; 153773 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Community Relations, 1986-1987; 153772 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park, 1987; 153771 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Drug Efforts, 1985-1986; 153770 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Notice about LaGuardia Statue, 1987; 153769 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Community Board 2, 1986; 153768 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Concerns, 1987; 153767 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Complaints RESTRICTED, 1986; 153766 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Memo on Photograph, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1987 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Commencement, 1986; 153765 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Governors Conference, Virginia Commonwealth University Commencement, 1985-1987; 153764 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Convocations, 1987-1987; 153763 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Corazon Aquino Event Thank Yous, 1986; 153762 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Founder's Day Convocation, 1987; 153761 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Awards, Special Events, 1987; 153760 (Box 162, Folder 6-7)
  - Muskie Lecture, 1986; 153759 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Special Event Planning, 1984-1986; 153758 (Box 162, Folder 9-11)
  - Hoosiers, 1987; 153757 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Colloquiums and Lectures, 1987; 153756 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Symposiums and Lectures, 1986; 153755 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1986-1987; 153754 (Box 163, Folder 4-5)
  - Invitation to Saul Bellow, 1986; 153752 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Petrie Lecture, 1986; 153751 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Liberty Weekend Conference, 1986; 153750 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science Centennial Convocation, 1986; 153749 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Report, 1987; 153748 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Basketball, School of Continuing Education Pamphlets, Mario Cuomo Address, 1986; 153747 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, Correspondence, Press Contact List, 1987; 153746 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, Memos, 1986; 153745 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Magazines, Newsletters, 1987; 153744 (Box 164, Folder 1-2)
  - Reports, Clippings, Memos, 1986; 153743 (Box 164, Folder 3-5)
  - Memos and Correspondence on New York University Magazine, 1987; 153742 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Memos, Correspondence and Drafts for New York University Magazine, 1986; 153741 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Condolences, 1986-1987; 153740 (Box 164, Folder 8-9)
  - Congratulatory Letter, 1987; 153738 (Box 164, Folder 10)
  - Thank You Letter, 1988; 153737 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Jessup Interview re: Nancy Hanks, 1986; 153736 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Interviews, 1986; 153735 (Box 165, Folder 3-5)
  - Memo on Trustee Escorts, 1988; 153734 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Dinners, 1986; 153723 (Box 165, Folder 7-9)
  - Interviews, 1987; 153722 (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
  - The Atlantic Council, 1986; 153721 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Penthouse Dinner, 1984; 153720 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - China Speech File, 1987; 153714 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Xiao Quian (Visit), 1985-1986; 153713 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - New York Academy of Sciences Event, 1986; 153712 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Statue of Liberty Centennial Event, 1986; 153711 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Dinners and Special Occasions, 1987; 153710 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Thank You Letters, 1986-1987; 153709 (Box 167, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1987; 153707 (Box 167, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1986; 153706 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Carl Davis Reception Event, 1987; 153705 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Aldernick Foundation Event (Conference), 1986; 153704 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1986; 153703 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Center for Latin American and Caribbean Studies Newsletter, 1987; 153702 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Invitation to Sir Harold Acton, 1986; 153701 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Invitations and Responses, 1987; 153700 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1987; 153699 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Declined Committee Invitations, 1986; 153698 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1987-1988; 153697 (Box 168, Folder 9-10)
  - Highlights of the Presidency of John Brademas at NYU, 1986; 153696 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Caring Community, 1988; 153695 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood Concerns, 1988; 153682 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Community Relations, 1988; 153681 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Letter from Community Board 2 on Local 3882 Strike, 1988; 153680 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Concerns, 1988; 153679 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Invitations to Spring Celebration, 1988; 153678 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, 1988-1988; 153677 (Box 169, Folder 7-8)
  - Letters to Elected Officials re: Virginia Commonwealth University Commencement Address, 1988; 153676 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - China Trip Notes, 1985; 153675 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Francois Mitterrand Convocation and Dinner, 1988; 153674 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Arts and Humanities Special Events, 1988; 153673 (Box 169, Folder 12-13)
  - Suzanne Waldmann Educational Communications Center Dedication, 1988; 153672 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Special Events, 1988; 153671 (Box 170, Folder 2-4)
  - Founder's Day Convocation, 1988; 153670 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1988; 153669 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, Clippings, 1988; 153668 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Voice of Experience Essay, 1988; 153667 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - New York University Magazine, 1988; 153666 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - NYU Today, 1988; 153665 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - NYU Today Publications, 1987-1988; 153664 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1988; 153663 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1988; 153662 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Invitations (M-Z), 1988; 153661 (Box 171, Folder 3-4)
  - Invitations (A - L), 1988; 153660 (Box 171, Folder 5-7)
  - Interviews, 1988; 153659 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Invitation Responses, 1991; 153658 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Invitations (J - Z), 1989; 153657 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1991; 153656 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Invitations to Boards and Committees, 1989; 153655 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Op-Ed on Limiting Congressional Terms, 1991; 153654 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, Memos, 1990; 153653 (Box 172, Folder 7-8)
  - News Clippings, Memos, Correspondence, 1989; 153652 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Thank You Letters, 1989-1990; 153650 (Box 173, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, 1991; 153648 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Memos, 1990; 153647 (Box 173, Folder 5-8)
  - Penthouse Dinners, 1989; 153646 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Dinners and Lectures, 1991; 153645 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Penthouse Dinners, 1990; 153644 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Interviews, Press Releases, 1990; 153643 (Box 174, Folder 2-4)
  - Interviews, 1989-1989; 153642 (Box 174, Folder 5-6)
  - Interviews, Events, 1991; 153641 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1989; 153640 (Box 223, Folder 8-9)
  - Public Occasions, 1990; 153639 (Box 175, Folder 1-2)
  - Public Occasions, 1991; 153638 (Box 175, Folder 3-4)
  - Public Occasions, 1989; 153637 (Box 175, Folder 5-7)
  - Memos, Wagner School Press Packet, 1989; 153636 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence on John von Neumann, 1991; 153635 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, 1990; 153634 (Box 176, Folder 3-5)
  - Conferences and Lectures, 1989; 153633 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1989-1991; 153632 (Box 176, Folder 7-9)
  - Dresden Conference, 1991; 153629 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Future of Europe Conference, 1990; 153628 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - "The Future of Europe", 1989; 153627 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Viewbook Request, 1990; 153626 (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Press Coverage, 1991; 153625 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence on Newsletters, 1989; 153624 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - New York University Press Related, 1990; 153623 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1991; 153622 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - New York University Press, 1989; 153621 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Memo on Robert McKay, 1991; 153620 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Publications, 1990; 153619 (Box 177, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence on Book Publication, 1989; 153618 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Forbes Response, 1986-1987; 153617 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Memos and Correspondence on Articles, 1989; 153616 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Memo on The Sciences Magazine, 1990; 153614 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Memos re: NYU Today Stories, 1990; 153613 (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Memos re: NYU Today Mailings, 1989; 153612 (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - Condolences, 1989; 153611 (Box 177, Folder 14)
  - Condolences, 1988; 153610 (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Leader Visits, 1990; 153609 (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1989; 153608 (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - Invitations (A - L), 1990; 153607 (Box 178, Folder 1-4)
  - Invitations (M - Z), 1990; 153605 (Box 178, Folder 5-7)
  - Invitations, 1991; 153606 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Invitations and Memos on Travel, 1990; 153604 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Invitations (A - I), 1989; 153603 (Box 179, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Events Attended RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 1-3)
  - Events Attended, 1984-1985 (Box 131, Folder 2-5)
  - Correspondence re: Council on Foreign Relations, 1984-1985 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Events Attended, 1984-1985 (Box 131, Folder 7-8)
  - Events Attended RESTRICTED, 1983-1985 (Box 134, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Memo, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1985-1987 (Box 135, Folder 3-6, Box 239, Folder 1)
  - President's Penthouse Events -- Invitation Lists, 1984-1985 (Box 131, Folder 10, Box 132, Folder 1)
  - President's Penthouse Events -- Invitation Lists and Information, 1984-1985 (Box 132, Folder 2-5)
  - President's Penthouse Events -- Invitation Lists and Letters, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Charles Bowsher Lecture/Dinner, October 10, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Event Documentation, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Citizen Participation Consultation -- NYU Conference, September 1983 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Television and Publication Interviews, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 1-2)
  - Marquesa Bona Frescobaldi Dinner, November 11, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence re: Annual Reports RESTRICTED, 1984-1985 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence re: Funding Development RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Invitations to Serve on Boards, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Events Invited To, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Interdepartmental Communication, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Interdepartmental Communication, 1987-1990 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Leadership, 1988, 1990, undated (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Brademas Writing and Comments, 1983-1984 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Brademas Writing and Comments, 1988-1989 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Notes -- Meetings, 1985, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Photographs -- Italy Trip, 1980s-1990s (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Photographs -- Dental School Scholarship Students and Brademas, 1984 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Photographs -- School of Continuing Education 50th Anniversary Celebration with Brademas and Others, 1984 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Photographs -- Brademas at Events, 1985-1988 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Photographs -- NYU and Universita degli Studi Venice Agreement Ceremony, 1987 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - Photographs -- Events, 1988, 1990 (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - Photographs -- Events, 1988-1989 (Box 254, Folder 7)
  - Photographs -- Events, 1990 (Box 254, Folder 8)
  - Photographs -- New York Italy Event, 1990 (Box 254, Folder 9)
  - Photographs -- Lecture at University of Thessaloniki, 1991-05-30 (Box 254, Folder 10)
  - Photograph -- Brademas and David Rockefeller, undated (Box 254, Folder 11)
  - Photographs -- Brademas with Mario Cuomo, Presentations, and Events, undated (Box 254, Folder 12)
  - Photographs -- Portraits of John Brademas, undated (Box 254, Folder 13)
  - Photographs -- Graduation Ceremony, undated (Box 254, Folder 14)
  - Photographs -- Onassis Center Event, 1980s (Box 254, Folder 15)
  - Photographs -- Elmer Holmes Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters Event, 1980s-1990s (Box 254, Folder 16)
  - Photographs -- Unknown Asian Country Trip, 1980s-1990s (Box 255, Folder 1-4, Box 256, Folder 2-4)
  - La Pietra -- Villa Exteriors, Other Villas, undated (Box 99, Video 1)
  - La Pietra -- Villa Exteriors, Interviews with Sir Harold, undated (Box 99, Video 2)
  - La Pietra -- Conversations with Sir Harold Acton, undated (Box 99, Video 3)
  - La Pietra -- Conversations with Sir Harold Acton, Duomo, Main House, and V. Olivi, undated (Box 99, Video 4)
  - La Pietra -- Conversations with Sir Harold Acton, Poem by Xuzimo, and Ponte Vecchio, undated (Box 99, Video 5)
  - La Pietra -- Villa I Tatti, Piazza Signoria Della, Stills of Villa and China, undated (Box 99, Video 6)
  - La Pietra -- Stills of Paintings, Conversations with Sir Harold Acton, and La Pietra Interiors, undated (Box 99, Video 7)
  - La Pietra -- Interiors, Conversation with Sir Harold Acton and Carter Brown, undated (Box 99, Video 8)
  - La Pietra -- Conversations with Sir Harold Acton and Carter Brown, and Stills of Villa, undated (Box 99, Video 9)
  - La Pietra -- Walk with Sir Harold Acton and Carter Brown, Palazzo Medici, Interview with Sir John Pope Hennessy and Carton Brown, and Birthday Party, undated (Box 99, Video 10)
  - La Pietra -- Dubs of La Pietra, undated (Box 99, Video 11)
  - La Pietra -- RAI: Villa La Pietra, Sir Harold Acton, Acton Project, Stock Footage WWII, Bridshead Revisited, Gertrude Stein, and Thasis, 1987-1988 (Box 99, Video 12)
  - La Pietra -- Oxford, The Last Aesthete, War Footage, Version 6, and Sample Titles, 1987 (Box 100, Video 13)
  - La Pietra -- Dub of On-line Video, Pachelbel, 1988 (Box 100, Video 14)
  - La Pietra -- Dub of On-line Video, Music, 1988 (Box 100, Video 15)
  - La Pietra -- Music, Version 6, 1988 (Box 100, Video 16)
  - La Pietra -- Version, Version 3 (Part 1 of 2), undated (Box 100, Video 17)
  - La Pietra -- Version 3 (Part 2 of 2), 2nd Rough Cut, Clean Version, 1 Hour Version (Part 1 of 2), undated (Box 100, Video 18)
  - La Pietra -- 1 Hour Version (Part 2 of 2), War Footage, Excerpts from Brideshead Revisited (Part 1 of 2), 1988 (Box 100, Video 19)
  - La Pietra -- Gertrude Stein, Thasis, First Rough Cut, 1988 (Box 100, Video 20)
  - La Pietra -- Florence Flood, Excerpt A Room with a View, Brideshead Revisited Episode 1 (Part 2 of 2), 1988 (Box 100, Video 21)
  - La Pietra -- Berenson, Music, undated (Box 100, Video 22)
  - La Pietra -- Music, undated (Box 100, Video 23)
  - La Pietra -- Music, Final Version, undated (Box 100, Video 24)
  - La Pietra -- Music E, Scratch Photos, undated (Box 101, Video 25)
  - La Pietra -- WWII British Troops in India, Sir Harold Acton PTZ Slides and Tape, The Last Aesthete, 1987-1988 (Box 101, Video 26)
  - La Pietra -- Dub of Rough Cuts, 1988 (Box 101, Video 27)
  - La Pietra -- Rough Cut, 1988 (Box 101, Video 28)
  - La Pietra -- 33:40 Version, 1988 (Box 101, Video 29)
  - La Pietra -- 1st Rough Cut Dub, Final Dub Absent Several Cues, Rough Cut, 1988 (Box 101, Video 30)
  - La Pietra -- Dub of La Pietra, Master British Film Institute, WWII British Troops in India, undated (Box 101, Video 31)
  - Brademas is Panelist on PBS Symposium "Art for Whose Sake?", 1989-04-14 (Box 101, Video 33)
- Series XI. Schools and Divisions, 1977-1991; 153318; 20.43 Linear Feet in 49 manuscript boxes.
  This series includes reports, speeches, correspondence, budgets, and annual reports collected by the Office of the President on individual NYU Schools and Divisions. Groups with the largest amount of material include the College of Arts and Sciences; College of Dentistry; Medical Center; Tisch School of the Arts; College and Graduate School of Business Administration; School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions; Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences; School of Law; School of Continuing Education; and Institute of Fine Arts. This series also contains files on NYU in Spain; the Gallatin Division; La Maison Française; Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies; and Deutsches Haus. Admissions reports on individual schools and the university date from 1977 to 1983. Meeting files for the Boards for the Medical Center, School of Arts and Science, and Law School Board are also in this series.
  - School of the Arts, 1980-1982; 153601 (Box 183, Folder 1-2)
  - School of the Arts -- Interactive Telecommunications Program, 1982; 153599 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1980-1982; 153598 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1981-1982; 153597 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Institute of French Studies, 1981-1982; 153596 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1981-1982; 153595 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - College of Business and Public Administration, 1980-1982; 153594 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1980-1982; 153593 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - School of Continuing Education, 1980-1982; 153592 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1980-1982; 153591 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - College of Dentistry, 1981-1982; 153590 (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Dean of Libraries, 1982-1986; 153589 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - President Brademas Reports, 1981; 153588 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - NYU Press, 1981; 153587 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence RESTRICTED, 1981-1986; 153586 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1985; 153585 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - College of Dentistry, 1980-1982; 153584 (Box 184, Folder 6-8)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions, 1980-1982; 153581 (Box 184, Folder 9-10)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions RESTRICTED, 1982; 153580 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - School of Law RESTRICTED, 1981-1982; 153578 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees of the Law Center Foundation, 1980-1982; 153577 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center RESTRICTED, 1980-1981; 153576 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Medical Center Administration RESTRICTED, 1980-1981 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - School of Medicine, 1980-1982; 153574 (Box 185, Folder 2-3)
  - Medical Center, 1980-1982; 153572 (Box 185, Folder 4-5)
  - Medical Center -- Howard Rusk, 1981-1982; 153570 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration RESTRICTED, 1981-1982; 153569 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - College of Arts and Science, 1981-1982; 153568 (Box 185, Folder 7-8)
  - College of Arts and Science RESTRICTED, 1979-1982; 153567 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - New York Institute for the Humanities RESTRICTED, 1981-1982; 153565 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - NYU Program in Spain, 1980-1982; 153564 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Division and Fellows, 1980-1982; 153563 (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - Tisch School of the Arts, 1982-1983; 153562 (Box 187, Folder 1)